I have been subjected to an insurance scam. This happened in
December last year or January this year,
sir. I already had a
Max Life
policy running for about two years.
I used to get calls from some of Max's agents or fake
employees, and they had
all my confidential information
like nominee details, policy number,
account number, premium, everything was available with
me, so I easily trusted them.
They got me two
policies done,
sir, saying that they would deactivate the current agent code
and transfer the customer code to the agent code.
With this, all my
bonus and agent commission would start getting
transferred to me every year. So, they got
me done about two policies, sir, one was
Aditya Birla's life insurance
and the other was Health Assure's medical
insurance. I have paid a total of about Rs. 90,000 till now
on these two policies. There are
about four employees, sir, who
talk to me at frequent intervals and give me advice.
Convincing me to take commissions and benefits and
they are still in touch with me so that I can get a
new policy from them and they say that
after taking this third policy there are some
benefits like in my name they
said that some interest acumatika
[Music]
[Music] A
huge scam is going on all over India
and many people like me have become victims of this.
This is a nexus of big scamsters
sir and these
big corporates like Max Life
and Aditya Bandla are
getting full support from these scamsters, that is why they are able to
survive for so long.
Sir, I have filed a complaint with Max Life,
Aditya Bandla and Health Isher
but all these companies have
refused to resolve my case because
their fee period has ended.
I request Insurance Masih to
support me in resolution
and help me in cancelling my policies and getting my
premium refunded.  Thank
you